galatta.com 2019-04-02

# Galatta.com - Privacy

#### Galatta.com's Privacy Policy - An Overview 

Galatta.com has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. We want to contribute to providing a safe and secure environment for all users of the internet as a whole and our web site in particular. All the sites owned and managed by our team have been included in this policy. This policy applies only to Galatta.com and other websites which carry the Galatta Brand and not to other companies' or organisations' web sites to which we link. 

#### Information Automatically Logged

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our Web site. Your IP address is also used to gather broad demographic information. Your IP address or demographic information is never shared with anyone or disclosed to third parties

#### Registration

You may provide us with certain information such as your name, email address, postal address when registering for certain services such as personalisation, chat, email, contests and promotions. This information will primarily be used for the purpose of providing personalisation and verification.

#### Feedback

Our site's feedback form requires users to give us contact information (like their name and email address) and demographic information (like their zip code, age or income level). We use customer contact information from the feedback form to send the user information about our company and promotional material from some of our partners.

Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site. We use this data to tailor the visitor's experience at our site, showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences.

The customer's contact information is also used to contact the user when necessary. Users may opt-out of receivingfuture mailings by sending us an e-mail.

#### Contests

We run contests on our site in which we ask visitors for contact information (like their email address), financial information (income bracket), and demographic information (like their zip code, age or income level).

We use contact data from our contestant to send information about our company and promotional material from some of our partners. The users contact information is also used by us to contact the visitor when necessary, primarily to announce new contests, contest results and site features.

Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site. We use this data to tailor our visitor's experience at our site, showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences.

A user may expressly choose to receive additional information from the contest organizer ( the website ) or the sponsor, in which the user identity is divulged to third party - as long as the user gives consent. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings by sending us an e-mail.

#### Electronic Newsletter

The site offers a free electronic newsletter to its users. We gather the e-mail addresses of users who voluntarily subscribe. Users may remove themselves from this mailing list by using the link provided in every newsletter.

#### Cookies

A cookie is a small data file that certain Web sites write to your hard drive when you visit them. A cookie file can contain information such as a user ID that the site uses to track the pages you have visited. But the only personal information a cookie can contain is information you supply yourself. A cookie can't read data off your hard disk or read cookie files created by other sites. Galatta.com uses cookies to track user traffic patterns and for the personalisation feature.

#### Registration:

When you register Galatta.com uses a cookie to store a unique, random user ID. We do not store passwords or any personal information about you. We use this ID to identify you anonymously in our database and to track the pages you visit on our site. Cookies also enable you to enter the sites ad use services as a member without having to log on each time.

If you have set your browser to warn you before accepting cookies, you will receive the warning message with each cookie. You can refuse cookies by turning them off in your browser. You do not need to have cookies turned on to use any Galatta.com site. 

#### Choice/Opt-Out policy

Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us and our partners at the point where we request information about the user. This site gives users the following options for removing their information from our database to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service.

#### Advertisers

We work with various third party advertising networks. These ads may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of our Web site, cookies received with banner ads are collected by advertising network, and we do not have any access to this information.

#### External Links

This site contains links to other sites. Galatta is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

#### Security

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. We make every effort to maintain quality of service and prevent misuse.

#### Children's Guidelines ( Children under 13 )

This site collects and uses personally identifiable information without prior verifiable parental consent. This site allows children to post or distribute any personally identifiable information without first obtaining verifiable parental consent.

#### Contacting the Web Site

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site or your dealings with this Web Site, you can contact

Webmaster Galatta.com  
DOT COM INFOWAY Pvt. Ltd.
